Guide to the Cornell University Council records, 1951-2008,
Cornell University Council records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University Council records, 1951-2008, 1951-1966 (bulk)
41-3-1020
Cornell University. Council.
13 cubic ft.,
Audio recordings, correspondence, printed materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes lists of members; organizational charts; material on the Council's functions and regulations; manuals; minutes of meetings; reports; and tape recordings of meetings and talks at Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes lists of members; organizational charts; material on the Council's functions and regulations; manuals; minutes of meetings; reports; and tape recordings of meetings and talks at Cornell University, including talks by Carl Sagan, Barber B. Conable, Donald G. Dickason, Richard M. Ramin, Deane W. Malott, Dale Corson, Morris Bishop, A. Henry Detweiler concerning the Sardis Expedition, and recordings of joint Council-Trustee meetings. Also program and pin for the Trustee-Council Annual Meeting, 2008. Also information pertaining to special events on campus such as dedications that would have been attended by members of the Council, invitation and participant lists for events are also included.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Bethe, Hans A. (Hans Albrecht), 1906-2005; Bishop, Morris, 1893-1973.; Conable, Barber B.; Corson, Dale R.; Detweiler, A. Henry, 1906-1970.; Dickason, Donald Garrett, 1931-; Malott, Deane Waldo, 1898-; Perkins, James Alfred, 1911-1998; Ramin, Richard M.; Sagin, Carl, 1934-; Archaeological Exploration of Sardis (Program); Cornell University -- Administration.; Cornell University -- Addresses, essays, lectures.; Cornell University. Board of Trustees.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Tapes of Council meetings are restricted to permission of the archivist.
NOTES
Includes collection 8-2-1359, which are Public Information Office records regarding the Council transferred to this collection. See collection #4-3-15 for other records of the Public Information Office.
CONTAINER LIST
- 41-3-1020, Cornell University Council records
  - Manual for Members of the Cornell University Council (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 1-2)
    Contain documents such as 1951 Autumn Meeting Questionnaire, Functions of the Council, Regulations of the Council, etc.
    Folder 1 contains more detailed documents than Folder 2. Also, Folder 2 has a copy of "A Handbook on Bequests and Life Income Agreements".
  - Cornell University Council Manual, 1958-1959 (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 3)
  - Cornell University Council Manual, 1959-1960 (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 4)
  - Cornell University Council Manual, 1960-1961 (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 5)
  - Cornell University Council Manual, 1962-1963 (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 6)
  - Cornell University Council Roster, 1953-1954 (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 7)
    Also contains an attendance list of the council meeting 1954, a list of invitations to non-council members, a list of local attendants of the council meeting, and one other document.
  - Cornell University Council Roster, 1954-1955 (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 8)
  - Cornell University Council Roster, 1955-1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 9-10)
    The two folders contain separate copies.
  - Cornell University Council Roster, 1965-1966 (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 11)
  - Cornell University Council Constitution August 1956 Revisions, 1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 12)
  - Cornell University Council Constitution April 1959 Revisions, 1959 (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 13)
  - Cornell University Council Constitution February 1961 Revisions, 1961 (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 14)
  - Cornell University Council Regulations, 1951 (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University Council Reports to Administrative Board Deans, Faculty, Staff, etc. (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 16)
  - Facts About Cornell, 1957-1961 (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 17)
    Contains "Cornell Facts" publication from the year 1957-1958, and "Facts About Cornell" publications from years 1958-1959, 1959-1960, and 1960-1961. Also, contains correspondences related to the publications, and other relevant documents.
  - Cornell University Council, 1955-1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 18)
    Contains miscellaneous documents such as reports to the administrative board by various departments/colleges, etc.
  - Cornell University Council, 1955-1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 1, Folder 19)
    Contains miscellaneous documents about the various meetings, such as programs, invitations, reports, and relevant publications.
  - Cornell University Council - Administrative Board, 1959-1962 (Box 41-3-1020 - 2, Folder 1)
    Contains documents like member lists, attendance sheets, etc.
  - Cornell University Council - Membership Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 41-3-1020 - 2, Folder 2)
    Contains documents such as letters to the committee members, election-related documents like suggested-members lists, etc.
  - Cornell University Council - Membership Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 41-3-1020 - 2, Folder 3)
  - Cornell University Council - Membership Committee, 1961-1962 (Box 41-3-1020 - 2, Folder 4-5)
    Contain documents such as letters to the committee members, election-related documents like suggested-members lists, etc.
  - Cornell University Council - Membership Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 41-3-1020 - 2, Folder 6)
  - Cornell University Council - Membership Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 41-3-1020 - 2, Folder 7-8)
  - Cornell University Council - Membership Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 41-3-1020 - 2, Folder 9)
  - Cornell University Council - Membership Committee (Box 41-3-1020 - 2, Folder 10)
    Contains miscellaneous documents: letters, lists, etc.
  - Cornell University Council - Nominating Committee, 1957-1962 (Box 41-3-1020 - 2, Folder 11)
    Contains nominee lists for each year's administrative board, relevant letters, etc.
  - Cornell University Council - Nominating Committee, 1962-1966 (Box 41-3-1020 - 2, Folder 12)
  - Cornell University Council Reporter, 1955-1957 (Box 41-3-1020 - 2, Folder 13)
    Contains various letters and publications.
  - Cornell University Council - Secondary Schools Committee, 1955-1961 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 1-3)
    Contain various documents, correspondences, reports, etc.
  - Cornell University - Regional Conference Correspondence and other Miscellaneous Documents, 1955-1962 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Utica Documents, 1955 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 5)
    Contains correspondences, fun raising program, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Massachusetts Documents, 1955 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Iowa Documents, 1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 7)
    Contains correspondences,some accounting documents, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Rochester Documents, 1955, 1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 8)
    Contains correspondences, member lists, alumni fund documents, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Chicago Documents, 1955, 1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 9)
    Contains correspondences, admission office statistics, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Buffalo Documents, 1955, 1957 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 10)
    Contains correspondences, publications, admission office statistics, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Wilmington Documents, 1955, 1957 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 11)
    Contains memorandums, and a correspondence.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Syracuse Documents, 1955, 1958 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 12)
    Contains correspondences, attendee lists, budget documents, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Minneapolis Documents, 1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Milwaukee Documents, 1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 14)
    Contains correspondences, member lists, budget documents, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, New England Documents, 1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 15)
    Contains correspondences, budget documents, admission office statistics, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Cleveland Documents, 1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Detroit Documents, 1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 17)
    Contains correspondences, budget documents, newspaper clippings, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Connecticut Documents, 1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Cincinnati Documents, 1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Nashville Documents, 1956, 1957 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 20)
    Contains correspondences, budget documents, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Philadelphia Documents, 1956, 1957 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Chicago Documents, Circa 1957 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 22)
    Contains correspondences, budget documents, agendas, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Texas Documents, 1956, 1960 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 23)
    Contains correspondences, budget documents, clippings, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Baltimore Documents, 1957 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Chicago Documents, 1958 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 25)
    Contains correspondences, publications, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Tennessee Documents, 1958 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 26)
    Contains correspondences.
  - "Cornell Comes to Akron", 1958 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 27)
    An invitation with a paid-response-card.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Indianapolis Documents, 1958 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 28)
    Contains correspondences and budget documents.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, New England Documents, 1958 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 29)
    Contains correspondences, conference program and attendees list.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Cincinnati Documents, 1959 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 30)
    Contains correspondences, conference program, budget documents, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, New England Documents, 1959 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 31)
    Contains registration documents and conference program.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Chicago Documents, 1959 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 32)
    Contains correspondences and conference program
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Atlanta, Chattanooga, Richmond Correspondences, 1958 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 33)
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Baltimore Documents, 1960 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 34)
    Contains correspondences, conference program, a report, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Kansas City Correspondences, 1960 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 35)
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Milwaukee Documents, 1960 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 36)
    Contains correspondences, conference program, member and volunteer lists, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Pittsburgh Documents, 1960 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 37)
    Contains correspondences, conference program, newspaper clippings, progress report, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, New York City Documents, 1960, 1962 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 38)
    Contains correspondences, budget documents, invitees list, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Cleveland Documents, 1961 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 39)
    Contains correspondences, conference program, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Northern New Jersey Documents, 1961 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 40)
    Contains correspondences, conference program, and a registration list.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Hartford Documents, 1961 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 41)
    Contains correspondences, conference program, a progress report, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Los Angeles Documents, 1961 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 42)
    Contains correspondences, conference program, memorandum, newspaper clippings, photos, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Detroit Documents, 1962 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 43)
    Contains correspondences, conference program, a report, newspaper clippings, photos, attendees list, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Nashville Correspondences, 1962 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 44)
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Detroit Memorandums, 1962 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 45)
  - Cornell Regional Conference, St. Louis Documents, 1962 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 46)
    Contains correspondences, admissions office statistics, conference program, a report, photos, budget documents, etc.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Chicago Documents, 1963 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 47)
    Contains the conference program, reports, newspaper clippings, etc. Also contains the negatives of Martin E Janis with Mayor Richard J. Daley on 2/14/1963, and with Cornell groups on 2/16/1963.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Chicago Accounting Documents, 1963 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 48)
    Contains various receipts and other budget related documents.
  - Cornell Regional Conference, Chicago Documents, 1963 (Box 41-3-1020 - 3, Folder 49)
    Contains correspondences, conference program, progress reports, etc.
  - Account 177 - Centennial Planning, 1960-1961 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 1)
    Contains paid vouchers and related documents.
  - Account 177 - Centennial Planning Committee Documents, 1961-1963 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 2)
  - Account 207 - Cornell Movie 1960, 1959-1960 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 3)
    Contains paid invoices and related correspondences.
  - Account 795 - Administrative Salaries Documents, 1963-1964 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 4)
  - Account 797 - Consulting Service Expense Documents, 1963-1964 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 5)
  - Account 799 - Cornell University Council, Prior to 11/1/1958 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 6)
  - Account 798 - Vice President Expense, 1958-1959 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 7)
  - Account 798 - Vice President Expense, 1959-1960 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 8)
  - Account 798 - Vice President Expense, 1960-1961 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 9)
  - Account 798 - Financial Documents, 1961-1962 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 10)
  - Account 798 - Financial Documents, 1962-1963 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 11)
    Contains correspondences and other documents.
  - Account 798 - Financial Documents, 1962-1963 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 12)
  - Account 798 - Financial Documents, 1963-1964 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 13)
  - Account 799 - Cornell University Council, 1958-1959 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 14)
  - Account 799 - Cornell University Council, 1959-1960 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 15-17)
  - Account 799 - Cornell University Council, 1960-1961 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 18)
  - Account 799 - Financial Documents, 1961-1962 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 19)
  - Account 799 - Financial Documents, 1962-1963 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 20)
  - Account 799 - Cornell University Council - Financial Documents, 1963-1964 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 21)
  - Account 800 - Cornell University Council, 1963-1964 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 22)
    Contains hourly expense documents.
  - Special Account 801, 1958-1960 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 23)
    Contains documents related to Kersting, Brown and Company, Inc., aside from other documents and possibly related correspondences.
  - Account 802 - F.N. Bard Recognition Dinner, 1959-1960 (Box 41-3-1020 - 4, Folder 24)
  - Cornell University Council - Annual Meetings Member Lists, 1953-1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 5, Folder 1)
    Contains a notebook, with handwritten members lists for 3rd-6th annual Council meetings.
  - Cornell University Council - 1st Annual Meeting Documents, 1951 (Box 41-3-1020 - 5, Folder 2)
    Contains correspondences, members, invitees, and attendees lists, propositions, and other documents.
  - Cornell University Council - 2nd Annual Meeting Documents, 1952 (Box 41-3-1020 - 5, Folder 3)
    Contains correspondences, members and attendees lists, newspaper clippings, publications, and other documents.
  - Cornell University Council - 3rd Annual Meeting Documents, 1953 (Box 41-3-1020 - 5, Folder 4)
    Contains correspondences, meeting program, attendees lists, transcriptions, Council roster 1953-1954, and other documents.
  - Cornell University Council - 4rth Annual Meeting Documents, 1954 (Box 41-3-1020 - 5, Folder 5)
    Contains correspondences, members and attendees lists, newspaper clippings, publications, meeting program, photos, and other documents.
  - Cornell University Council - 5th Annual Meeting Documents, 1955 (Box 41-3-1020 - 5, Folder 6)
    Contains correspondences, writings, a copy of Cornell Alumni News Volume 58, No. 5, members lists, newspaper clippings, meeting program, photos, and other documents.
  - Cornell University Council - 6th Annual Meeting Documents, 1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 5, Folder 7)
    Contains addresses, meeting program, some publications, and other documents.
  - Cornell University Council - 6th Annual Meeting Documents, 1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 5, Folder 8)
    Contains correspondences, a report, members and attendees lists, and other documents.
  - Cornell University Council - Chairman John P. Syme Annual Report, 1956 (Box 41-3-1020 - 5, Folder 9)
  - Cornell University Council - 7th Annual Meeting Documents, 1957 (Box 41-3-1020 - 5, Folder 10)
    Contains addresses, correspondences, meeting program, members and attendees lists, newspaper clippings, photos, and other documents.
  - Cornell University Council - 7th Annual Meeting Documents, 1957 (Box 41-3-1020 - 5, Folder 11)
    Contains the meeting program, and detailed documents related to J.L. Zwingle's slide presentation.
  - Cornell University Council - 8th Annual Meeting Documents, 1958 (Box 41-3-1020 - 5, Folder 12)
    Contains speeches, correspondences, meeting program, and other documents.
  - Cornell University Council - 1st Regional Meeting, NYC - Documents, 1952 (Box 41-3-1020 - 5, Folder 13)
    Contains a summary of the speech by Dean Paul M. O'Leary, correspondences, attendees list, a publication from Cornell Alumni News, and other documents.
  - Cornell University Council - Chairman Edwin T. Gibson's Annual Report (Box 41-3-1020 - 5, Folder 14)
  - Cornell University Council - Archives, 1951-1955 (Box 41-3-1020 - 5, Folder 15)
    Contains documents related to annual meetings, correspondences, and other documents.
  - Cornell University Council - 9th Annual Meeting Documents, 1959 (Box 41-3-1020 - 6, Folder 1)
    Contains samples of materials used in a display of state college publications in Statler Inn.
  - Cornell University Council - 9th Annual Meeting Documents, 1959 (Box 41-3-1020 - 6, Folder 2)
    Contains sample of registration kits, a member roster and another document.
  - Cornell University Council - 9th Annual Meeting Documents, 1959 (Box 41-3-1020 - 6, Folder 3)
    Contains a report, addresses, meeting program, correspondences, and other documents
  - Cornell University Council - 10th Annual Meeting Documents, 1960 (Box 41-3-1020 - 6, Folder 4-5)
    Contain a report, attendees list, meeting program, correspondences, a copy of Cornell Daily Sun, Vol. LXXVII, No. 15, and Cornell Crescent, Vol. 25, and other documents.
    The two folders contain many of the same documents and publications.
  - Cornell University Council - 12th Annual Meeting Documents, 1962 (Box 41-3-1020 - 6, Folder 6)
    Contains a report, the meeting program, correspondences, a copy ILR Research, Volume 8, No. 1; Ithaca Journal, 147th Year, No. 235; of a special edition of Cornell Daily Sun, and other documents.
  - Cornell University Council - 12th Annual Meeting Documents, 1962 (Box 41-3-1020 - 6, Folder 7)
    Contains a report, correspondences, welcoming remarks of Harold Brayman, the Council Chairman, and other documents.
  - Cornell University Council - 12th Annual Meeting Documents, 1962 (Box 41-3-1020 - 6, Folder 8)
    Contains the master list, and some other documents.
  - Cornell University Council - 15th Annual Meeting Documents, 1965 (Box 41-3-1020 - 6, Folder 9)
    Contains correspondences, members roster, members geographic summary, council's constitution, and other documents.
  - Cornell University Council - 16th Annual Meeting Documents, 1966 (Box 41-3-1020 - 6, Folder 10-11)
    Contains correspondences, attendees roster, invitees list, housing-related and other documents.
  - Cornell University Council - Administrative Board, 1965 (Box 41-3-1020 - 6, Folder 12)
    Contains meetings' minutes, agendas, notifications, correspondences, and other related documents.
  - Cornell University Council - Administrative Board, 1966 (Box 41-3-1020 - 6, Folder 13)
  - Cornell University Council - Administrative Board, 1965-1967 (Box 41-3-1020 - 6, Folder 14)
    Contains miscellaneous correspondences and related documents.
  - Cornell University Council - Sample Letters (Box 41-3-1020 - 6, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University Council - Membership Letters, etc. (Box 41-3-1020 - 6, Folder 16)
  - Various Account Ledgers (Box 41-3-1020 - 6, Folder 17)
- 8-2-1359, Public Information Office records regarding the Council
  - Special Events, 1962-1963: Cornell University Council. Miscellaneous Correspondence and Accounts
    - General List for EEC (European Economic Community, Common Market) Conference, 1962 (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 1)
    - Thanking Arthur H. Dean for Conference (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 2)
    - Conference Correspondence (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 3)
    - Delegate Declination (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 4)
    - Common Market Conference, April 4-5, 1962 (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 5)
    - Delegate List (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 6)
    - Acceptance (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 7)
    - Awaiting Decision (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 8)
    - Signed by Arthur H. Dean (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 9)
    - Invitees (General) (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 10)
    - Declinations (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1961 - 1962 (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 12)
    - Finalized Lists, E.E.C. (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 13)
    - Hosts (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 14)
    - Participants, Hosts, Delegates, Invitees (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 15)
    - Misc. Common Market (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 16)
    - Common Market Pending (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 17)
    - Participants - European and United States (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 18)
    - Hosts, Delegates, Invitees, Participants (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 20)
    - Invitee Lists (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 21)
    - List #1 (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 22)
    - Conference List (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 23)
    - Conference Space - Responses Invitee List #1 (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 24)
    - Conference Space - Responses Invitee List #2 (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 25)
    - Conference on Space Exploration (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 26)
    - Conference Space - Invitee List # (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 27)
    - Misc. Conference Papers (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 28)
    - Conference Scheduled for November (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 29)
    - Conference Space (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 30)
    - Conference - November 8 and 9 at Ithaca (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 31)
    - Conference Space Invitation Responses (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 32)
    - Conference Space Program (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 33)
    - Council Administrative Board (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 34)
    - Council (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 35)
    - Council, 1964-1965 (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 36)
    - Council and Summary Sheets, 1964-1965 (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 37)
    - Council #799 - Summary Sheets (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 38)
    - Council - Supplies, incl. Mimeo, Printed Materials (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 39)
    - Council - Admin. Board Meetings (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 40)
    - Council - Travel (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 41)
    - Council - Postage (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 42)
    - Council - Misc. (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 43)
    - CU Council 799 (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 44)
    - Collacott, Robert H. - CUC Expense (Box 8-2-1359 - 1, Folder 45)